Guide to the Yale University Library Personnel Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library personnel records
1909-2008
RU 100
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
242.75
The records consist of personnel files of former employees maintained by Library Human Resources, Yale University.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-H (YRG 32-H), Yale University Library personnel records.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of personnel files of former employees maintained by Library Human Resources, Yale University.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Academic libraries; Librarians; Library employees; Library personnel management; Yale University -- Employees; Yale University. Library
- Personnel records, 1909-1976; Accession 19ND-A-334
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2052
  - Boxes 1-10, not inventoried (Box 1–10)
  - 1942 Shi-Y (Box 11)
  - 1943
    - B-H (Box 11)
    - J-Z (Box 12)
  - 1944
    - B-P (Box 13)
    - R-Y (Box 14)
  - 1945
    - B-G (Box 14)
    - H-W (Box 15)
  - 1946
    - B-C (Box 15)
    - D-Y (Box 16)
  - 1947
    - B-S (Box 17)
    - T-W (Box 18)
  - 1948
    - B-E (Box 18)
    - F-Y (Box 19)
  - 1949
  - 1950
    - Y (Box 23)
  - 1951
  - 1952
  - 1953
  - Boxes 20-28, not inventoried (Box 20–28)
  - 1954
    - F-R (Box 29)
    - S-W (Box 30)
  - 1955
    - B
    - C-K (Box 31)
    - L-S (Box 32)
    - T-Z (Box 33)
  - 1956
    - B-F (Box 33)
    - G-N (Box 34)
    - O-S (Box 35)
    - T-Z (Box 36)
  - 1957
    - B-D (Box 36)
    - E-K (Box 37)
    - L-R (Box 38)
  - 1958
  - 1959
  - 1960
  - 1961
  - 1962
  - 1963
  - Boxes 39-74, not inventoried (Box 39–74)
  - 1965
  - 1966
  - 1967
  - 1968
  - 1969
  - 1970
  - 1971
  - 1972
  - 1973
  - 1974
  - 1975
  - 1976
- Personnel records, 1977; Accession 1981-A-056
- Personnel records, 1978; Accession 1981-A-061
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2054
- Personnel records, 1979; Accession 1983-A-105
- Personnel records, 1984-1988; Accession 1991-A-080
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2064
- Personnel records, 1980; Accession 1983-A-104
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2056
- Personnel records, 1981; Accession 1985-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2057
- Personnel records, 1982; Accession 1986-A-088
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2058
- Personnel records, 1983; Accession 1987-A-063
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2059
- Personnel records, 1984; Accession 1987-A-064
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2060
- Personnel records, 1985; Accession 1989-A-008
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2061
- Personnel records, 1986; Accession 1989-A-059
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2062
- Personnel records, 1970-1984; Accession 1989-A-090 (Box 1–3)
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Personnel records, 1987; Accession 1990-A-082
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2063
- Personnel records, 1985-1988; Accession 1991-A-114
- Personnel records, 1989; Accession 1992-A-055
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
- Personnel records, 1990; Accession 1993-A-028
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2066
- Personnel records, 1991; Accession 1994-A-109
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2067
- Personnel records, 1992; Accession 1995-A-073
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2068
  - 1992 (Box 2, Folder 184)
- Personnel records, 1993; Accession 1996-A-080
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2069
- Personnel records, 1994-1995; Accession 1997-A-079
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
- Personnel records, 1996; Accession 2001-A-078
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
- Personnel records, 1997; Accession 2002-A-014
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2073
- Personnel records, 1997-1998; Accession 2002-A-100
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2074
- Personnel files, promotion review and grievance records, 1989-1999; Accession 2003-A-026
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2075
  - PROMOTION REVIEW (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 206)
      - PROMOTION REVIEW 1994 (Box 6, Folder 207)
      - PROMOTION REVIEW OLD (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - STUDENT/CASUAL TERMS (Non-permanent records) (Box 7, Folder 291)
- Personnel records, 1996-2001; Accession 2004-A-092
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2077
  - 2000 STUDENT/CASUAL
  - Promotion Review 2002
  - Promotion Review 1996-1999
  - 1997/2001 Promotion Review
  - 2001 Promotion Review
- Personnel records, 2002; Accession 2005-A-199
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2078
- Personnel records, 2003-2004; Accession 2006-A-229
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2080
- Personnel records, 2005; Accession 2007-A-116
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2081
- Promotion records, 2005-2006; Accession 2008-A-120
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2082
- Promotion review files, 2007; Accession 2008-A-167
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2083
- Library personnel records, 2007; Accession 2009-A-005
- Personnel records, 2006; Accession 2009-A-031
  Restricted until Jan 2, 2082
- Personnel records, 2007-2008; Accession 2010-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2084